{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262743228","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262743228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262743615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262743614"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262743851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262743851"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262744168","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262744168"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262744403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262744402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262747804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262747804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262748097","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262748097"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262749001","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262749001"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262749424","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262749424"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262752340","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262752339"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262752622","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262752622"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262753465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262753465"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262754128","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262754128"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262754862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262754861"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262755186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262755186"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262755463","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262755463"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262755782","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262755782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262756049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262756049"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262759757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262759757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262760141","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262760141"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262760376","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262760376"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262760690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262760689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262760925","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262760925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262764364","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262764364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIZI"," userResponse":" HIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262764658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262764658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262765562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262765562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HERUFI"," userResponse":" HERUFI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262765998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262765997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hizi ni herufi kuu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262768942","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262768941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMKA"," userResponse":" TAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262769231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262769230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262770086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262770086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAUTI"," userResponse":" SAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262770765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262770764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUU"," userResponse":" KUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262771515","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262771514"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262771854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262771853"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262772138","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262772137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262772465","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262772464"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262772742","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262772741"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262776182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262776180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262776281","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262776281"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b63c0341-2fb4-4c20-b0aa-7b83e072dddf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__LC_Vowel_Song_1__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Tamka kwa sauti kuu a e i o u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262787332","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262787332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262787566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262787565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262788543","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262788543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262789830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262789829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262792774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262792774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262793634","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262793634"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262793957","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262793956"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262795191","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262795191"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262798784","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262798783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262799783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262799782"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262800036","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262800036"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262800988","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262800987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262803909","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262803909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262804954","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262804953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262805435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262805435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262809956","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262809954"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262810045","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262810045"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" bc18d831-1a5a-4c8f-8697-1d1aa71ca744"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_1"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262822732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262822731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262824723","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262824723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262826326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262826326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262828406","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262828406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262829998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262829997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262832224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262832223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262833831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262833831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262836009","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262836009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262837625","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262837625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262839798","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262839797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262841828","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262841827"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262841932","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262841932"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 3e0dea77-78d4-4fce-8228-6e94eb44015c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__vow.A..Z.asc.lc.5__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262851926","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262851926"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262856696","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262856696"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_4-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262861235","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262861235"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262866246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262866245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262968937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262968937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262975422","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262975422"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_1-0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262979817","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262979817"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262984384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262984384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_9-8"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262989499","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262989499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_3-2"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548262993792","data":{"timestamp":" 1548262993792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.gl:dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263000280","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263000278"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 16547e53-f6fe-436a-adae-cfb7585e164f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.gl_dot.0..9.GL_SD_OFF1_L.bub2.6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_4_5-4"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263018595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263018595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_e-a-i"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263022921","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263022921"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_u-o-e"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263026373","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263026373"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_a-u-i"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263030126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263030126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_o-i-u"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263033569","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263033569"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263039322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263039321"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263080389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263080388"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" b5ff34e1-4a83-4ee8-8fcd-4aaaea427312"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.all.stat.show.23__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_u_a-i-u"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263089306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263089305"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-d-e"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263092870","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263092870"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263098275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263098275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_b-p-d"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263101806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263101806"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-w-r"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263105071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263105071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-b"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263108362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263108362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 5"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548263114125","data":{"timestamp":" 1548263114124"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190123_195845"," gameId":" 35646c87-c52c-4b41-bbae-01607a4af712"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.vow.asc.sim.stat.show.24__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_e_c-e-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}